MUHAMMAD GYMNASTIAR

UNIVERSITY STUDENT

+62 858-0713-0004

muhammadgym23@gmail.com

Muhammad Gymnastiar

Sandung, West Java

Summary

An active Mathematics undergraduate student at Universitas Padjadjaran with strong English proficiency and solid communication skills. Experienced in working collaboratively within teams and managing tasks effectively. Passionate about leadership, global relations and storytelling, with a demonstrated ability to write, edit, and communicate professionally in various settings.

Education Kab. Sumedang

Universitas Padjajaran 2022 - Present

Mathematics Undergraduate Program

SMA Negeri 1 Bandung

2019-2022

Natural Science Class

Experience

Himatika FMIPA Unpad Jatinangor, Indonesia January 2024 - Present

President

Chairman

Lead 90+ members in designing and implementing work programs using the OKR framework. Maintain organizational values and culture while engaging with alumni, faculty, and student associations. Foster a supportive environment for learning and resilience, managing 5 divisions, 12 departments, and 2 bureaus with ongoing work meetings and knowledge sharing.

Majelis Perwakilan Anggota Himatika FMIPA Unpad Chairman

Jatinangor, Indonesia January 2023 - January 2024

Responsible for supervising and coordinating 54 work programs implemented by PH Himatika. has carried out a comprehensive evaluation and study of Himatika Legal Products and has become a liaison between Himatika Members and related institutions by carrying out Aspiration and Advocacy functions.

BEM Kema FMIPA Unpad Staff of Research and Data Bureau

Jatinangor, Indonesia April 2023 - Maret 2024

Responsible for the work program of the BEM Kema FMIPA Unpad Website. Designed a database that is integrated with the website for BEM Kema FMIPA Unpad administrators

with the website for BEM Kema FMIPA Unpad administrators. Majelis Perwakilan Kelas SMA Negeri 1 2020-2021

Reviewed organization deficiency, start from change the Memorandum of Association and improved the existence and efficiency of the organization from years before. Has succeeded in being responsible for supervising Student Council Board projects.

Leadership and Activities

OSEAN FMIPA Unpad

Head of Accommodation

Jatinangor, Indonesia

June 2023 - September 2023

Oversees logistics, public relations, security, and medical divisions, coordinating with faculty for permits and security. Serves as the primary liaison for 10 student associations in sports, esports, and art competitions, manages university security, and handles vendor relations for event logistics.

Jatinangor, Indonesia

PMB Universitas Padjadjaran

August 2023

Facilitator

Served as an MC, engaging around 500+ new students through welcoming speeches and introductions. As the face of the event, I welcomed and engaged the incoming students, creating a warm and inclusive atmosphere, Jatinangor, Indonesia

Musyawarah Besar Akhir Tahun Himatika FMIPA Unpad

December 2022 - January 2023

Project Officer

Oversee and coordinate with each division in it's every progress for the event. Supported the division's job for the continuation of the event. Planned and executed a successful year-end conference.

Jatinangor, Indonesia

Proyek Angkatan (Union Social Care and Activities)

October 2022

Head of Public Relation Division

Arranged all of the external communication properly, take care of relationships with related parties and surveyed for event location. Coordinating with other division to ensure smooth execution of events

11-14 August 2022

HARNAS UMKM Volunteer

Played a crucial role in preparing for the reception of VIP guests, including the Governor of West Java and the Minister of Cooperatives and Small and Medium Enterprises of Indonesia.

Bandung, Indonesia

PPRPG Gideon July - December 2021

PDG XLII Commander

Led the 'Pendidikan Dasar' event from planning to execution, coordinating the committee and overcoming pandemic challenges. Engaged alumni for technical, accommodation, and sponsorship support, while liaising with professional medical teams for COVID-19 tests and vaccinations. Managed logistics and operations on the day of the event, ensuring all safety protocols were followed.

Certificates

Learning How to Learn: Powerful mental tools to help you master tough subjects

Issued Jan 2024

Semifinalist at "Mathematics Calculus Competition 7.0" National Level

Issued Oct 2023

EF SET Certificate (C2 Proficient, 73/100)

Issued Sep 2024

GO Programming Language from Great Learning

Issued Sep 2024

Cryptography I from Stanford University

Issued Oct 2024

Data Analytics Essential from Cisco

Issued Nov 2024

Algorithms Specialization from Stanford University

Issued Dec 2024

Hard Skills

- Copywriting
- Project Management
- Microsoft Office

Soft Skills

- Communication
- Adaptive
- Work Ethic
- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Problem Solving

Language

Bahasa Indonesia - Native speaker

English - Intermediate

Dutch - Beginner